拉尔斯
的头
欢迎关注微博@UUU字幕组，获取最新熟肉信息！
出品
UUU字幕组
翻译
饼干一枚
校对
Husky
特效
presisco
压制
刚才发生了什么?
What the heck just happened?
拉尔斯!
Lars!
你救了我们!
You saved us!
你阻止了那些机器们, 但, 但它们其中一只爆炸了
You stopped the Robonoids, but -- but one of them exploded,
然 然后你就不动了, 然后我就开始哭
and -- and you weren't moving, and I started crying.
我还让你复活了!
I brought you back to life!
虽然是个意外
It was an accident.
我是说, 我如果知道我有这能力
I mean, I probably would've done that on purpose
我肯定会让你复活的
if I had known I could do that,
但是我没有经过你的允许, 所以对不起
but I didn't really ask your permission, so I'm sorry.
让我复活
Back to life?
你是说…我还死过?
So I was... away from life?
啊!
Aah!
我变粉了!
I'm pink!
啊 我知道 你感觉怎么样?
Ah! I know. Do you feel okay?
我也不是特别知道
I don't really know.
但你的身体, 你痛吗?
But your body, are you sore?
不痛
No.
你觉得累吗?
Are you tired?
不累
No.
-那你感觉舒服不?  -不舒服
-Do you feel good? -No.
-你那你感觉难受吗?  -啥感觉都没有!
-Do you feel bad? -No!
我只是感觉被吓得有点懵
I guess I just feel really freaked out.
呃, 我也是, 至少咱俩这点是一样的
Well, I am, too, so at least we're on the same page here.
它们回来了
They're back.
那些粉碎机器们又来了!
Those shattering Robonoids are back!
快点
Quickly.
把入口堵上
Block the entrance.
拉尔斯, 你待在这休息下
Lars, you stay here and rest.
好吧
All right.
我预言拉尔斯会变色
I predict Lars will change in hue.
真是个谜!
What a mystery!
哇噢 力气真大
Whoa, strong.
这真的可以挡住他们吗?
Is this gonna be enough?
它们好像没瞅到咱们
They seem to have overlooked us
暂时如此
for the time being.
快点, 堵上入口!
Quickly, block the entrance!
只要我在这里, 它们还是要来找我们
As long as I'm here, they're gonna keep coming after us.
没错, 这个主意糟透了
It's true. This was a horrible plan.
我们该找个新的藏身之所吗?
Should we try to find a new hiding spot?
别别别! 如果我们离开这个洞穴
No, no, no! If we leave this cavern,
我们就会完全暴露的
we'll be completely exposed.
但我们如果一直呆在这
But if we stay here,
它们迟早会发现我们的
they'll find us for sure.
所以我们要么呆在这被抓起来
So, we either stay here and get caught...
要么出去被抓起来
Or we go out there and get caught.
打住, 我现在是个僵尸了?
So, wait, am I a zombie now?
不是
No.
呃…你不是!
Well...no!
你会说话, 僵尸就不会说话
You can talk, and zombies can't do that.
我一定是把你治愈了
I must've healed you.
我以前治愈过人类, 只是从来没有这么夸张
I've healed people before, just never this much.
承认吧, 史蒂文! 我已经是只僵尸了!
Just admit it, Steven! I'm a zombie!
噢 我知道了
Oh, I know.
僵尸不会有心跳的
A zombie wouldn't have a heartbeat.
这 呃 跳的太慢了点
That's, uh, pretty slow.
但我觉得我们可以排除变成粉色僵尸这个可能
But I think we can rule out pink zombie.
我的星星啊
Thank the stars.
什么是僵尸
What's a zombie?
我真不敢相信 人类可以像这样变色
I can't believe humans just change color like this.
人类不会变色
They don't.
呃 但是非常冷的时候皮肤会变蓝
Well, I guess if you get really cold, you turn blue,
非常尴尬的时候就会变得很红
and if you get really embarrassed, you turn red.
那变成粉色是代表什么?
So what does pink mean?
是代表拉尔斯会爆炸吗?
Is Lars gonna explode or something?
或许爆炸之后拉尔斯再重生会变个颜色
Maybe then Lars will reform with a different color.
我打赌不管拉尔斯选择变成什么颜色
I'm sure whatever color Lars chooses
都会很可爱的
will be lovely.
但为什么我是粉色的?
But why am I pink?
你甚至连头发颜色都变了
Even your hair is different.
啊! 刚才那是什么?
Aah! What was that?
哈? 刚才是闪了一下, 对吧?
Huh? It, like, lit up, right?
你也看到了吧
You saw it, too.
看到了
Uh, yeah.
你刚才做了什么? 再来一遍
What did you do? Do it again.
它为什么会这样
Why is it doing that?
拉尔斯, 我觉得我知道这是什么了
Lars, I think I know what this is.
有些事我可以尝试下, 但是 还是不了
There's something I can try, but no.
你不会想让我进你脑袋里的
You don't want me going in your head.
你又要侵占我的身体?
You're going to possess me again?
不, 刚才那句话只是字面意思
No. It would be more literal.
-那是什么意思?   -别管了
-Then what is it? -Forget it.
听着史蒂文, 我不会生气的好吗
Look, Steven, - I'm not gonna get mad, okay?
我相信你 只要能把我从这里救出去就好
I trust you. Just help me out here.
我想知道 我是不是真的有魔法头发
If I've got magic hair now, I want to know.
所有人退后
Everyone stand back.
好吧, 你现在弯下来
All right, now just bend down.
这样吗
Like this?
现在你可能会感到一只轻微的脚在你脑袋里
Now, you might feel - a slight foot in your head.
等等, 轻微的啥
Wait, what?
发生了什么
What is happening?
他们在融合
They're fusing!
他们在融合对吧?
They're fusing, right?
你做的很好, 拉尔斯
You're doing great, Lars.
呃, 成吧
Uh, okay.
啊 我到家了
Ah. I'm home.
我到家啦!
I'm home!
大家?
Guys?
她们哪儿去了
Where are they?
水!
Water!
啊
Ahh.
吃的
Food.
生活真美好
Life is beautiful!
带点给拉尔斯
Got to bring some back for Lars.
真希望我可以告诉她们我还好
Wish I could tell everyone I'm okay.
狮子
Oh, Lion.
所以你--
So you were --
我的天, 我--我有太多东西想问你
Gosh, there -- there's so much I want to ask you.
真希望你会说话
If only you could talk.
谢谢你, 兄弟
Thanks, buddy.
-啊!  -啊!
-Aah! -Aah!
抱歉, 拉尔斯
Sorry, Lars.
所以怎么了, 我脑袋里有什么?
So what happened? What's in my head?
-家 -啥?
Home. - Wha?
大家, 我有个重大发现
Everyone, I've made an amazing discovery!
我刚回到了地球
I just traveled back to planet Earth
从拉尔斯的脑袋里穿过去的
by going through Lars' head!
你回到地球了? 什么鬼?
You went back to Earth? What the heck?
我脑袋是个虫洞?
Is my head like a wormhole?
不, 比那个要简单得多
No, it's way simpler than that.
你知道, 我有只粉红色的狮子
You see, I have a pink pet lion
当我妈还在的时候 他是我妈的
who belonged to my mom when she was still here,
结果我发现我可以进入他的鬃毛里
and it turns out I can go into his mane,
然后它把我送到一个魔法空间
and it transports me to a magical dimension
那里有带有一棵树的山和我妈妈留下来的东西
where my mom kept a bunch of artifacts on a hill with a tree,
不知道为什么, 我不能在那里呼吸
and for some reason, I can't breathe in there.
不管怎样, 当我进入拉尔斯的脑袋里
But anyway, when I went into Lars' head,
我就被传送到同一个魔法空间
I got transported to the same magical dimension,
但是是一个新的区域, 和以前那个是联通的
but it was a new part of it, but since the two are connected,
我可以从这里到狮子的鬃毛里
I could reach the portal that leads out of Lion's mane,
然后回到地球
which is back on Earth!
呃...
Uh...
来, 我给你带了些吃的
Here, I brought you some food.
哈? 谢谢-我留着等会吃吧
Huh? Thanks, - but I-I'll save it for later.
你不饿吗?
But aren't you hungry?
或许你也像狮子那样只吃魔法蜥蜴
Maybe you only eat magical lizards now like Lion.
你 你想吃蜥蜴吗?
A-Are you hungry for lizards?
不, 我不想吃蜥蜴
No, I do not want a lizard.
但你已经几天都没吃东西了
But you haven't eaten in days.
我知道
I know.
我肚子里应该是有什么粉色魔法之类的
There must be pink magic in my guts now or something.
这个盒子是什么
What is this box?
这是果汁 这是我们在地球上的喝的
It's juice. - We drink it back on Earth.
-什么?  -这不可能
-What? -That's impossible.
-不可能的 -没门
-There's no way. -Unh-unh.
史蒂文回来啦
Steven's back.
不可能的
That can't be.
难以置信
I'm incredulous.
为什么不可以
Why can't it be?
所有人都知道 地球…
Everyone knows that the Earth...
被钻石们的攻击摧毁了!
Was decimated by the Diamond attack!
抱歉
Sorry.
并不是那样的
It's not like that.
钻石们的确袭击了地球
The Diamonds did attack,
但是仍然有宝石们住在那儿
but there are still Gems living on Earth,
地球也生机勃勃
and the planet's full of life.
地球上长出了土豆 变成了这些薯片
It grew the potatoes that becames this chips
地球上长出了小麦 最终变成了面粉
It grew the wheat that eventually became the flour
然后最终变成了面包
that eventually became the bread
最后还被做成了三明治
that eventually became this sandwich!
-三… -明治?
-Sand... -Wich?
但为什么还有宝石想住在那里?
But why would Gems still live there?
因为地球是一个可以做自己的地方
Because the Earth is a place where we can be ourselves.
我们可以自由生活 不用因自己的不同而躲藏
We can live freely without having to hide who we are.
自由生活?
Live freely?
不需要躲藏?
Without having to hide?
听起来真好啊
That sounds wonderful.
就是这么好
It is.
现在我们有了这个传送门, 我们就可以全都去那里
And now that we have this portal, we can all go there.
全部?
All?
我该怎么穿过我自己的脑袋?
How am I supposed to go through my own head?
哦 嗯
Oh. Hmm.
住手! 你要把我胳膊给卸下来了!
Stop! You're gonna break my elbow!
好吧, 这样行不通, 肯定还有其他办法
Okay, so that didn't work, but I'm sure there's another way.
等等, 听着, 我明白了
No, no, look. I get it.
所有人都走, 我呆在这里就可以了
Everyone just go, and I'll stay here.
没有别的办法了 还是我来
There's no other way out. I'm it.
地球比这里好太多
The Earth is way better than this.
那里没有飞来飞去的机器
There's no robots flying around.
只有在日落时翱翔天际的海鸥
Just seagulls that fly in front of the sunset
非常美!
and it's beautiful!
走吧, 你们会懂的
Just go, you'll see.
我以前都没在乎过这些, 别错过这个机会
I took it for granted, so don't pass up this chance.
如果你执意这样
Well, if you insist.
我们不会这么做
We won't do it.
我们不会独留你一人的
Not if it means leaving you behind.
什么? 我还想做个伟大牺牲呢
What?! I'm trying to perform a beautiful act over here.
我们了解这个星球
We know this planet.
我们已经在这些隧道里躲了亿万年
We've been hiding in these tunnels for eons.
你需要我们帮助你逃离这里
You'll need us to help you get around.
再说, 我们这些残品都是一家人
Besides, us off colors stick together.
我们会通过其他办法去地球
We'll get to Earth another way.
我们会找到另一条路的
We'll find an alternate route.
但是你必须得回去
But you've got to go back.
但是不能就把你留在这里啊
But it doesn't feel right to just leave you here.
你说过这个星球上的每个人
You said yourself - that everyone on this planet
就是为了抓你
is out to get you.
直到你回到地球之前你都不会安全
You won't be safe - until you're back on Earth.
但拉尔斯--
But, Lars --
别和我吵!
Don't argue with me!
你总是试着来帮我
You're always trying to help me.
你还让我复活了
You brought me back to life.
就让我做个值得拥有这一切的人吧
Just let me be somebody who deserved it.
好吧 我会告诉大家你很好
All right, - I'll tell everyone you're okay.
我会回来的 我可以带来你所需要的东西
I'll be back. - I can bring whatever you need.
都小心点, 好吗
Be careful, okay?
我们会的
We will.
我们不能丢下拉尔斯啊!
We can't leave without Lars!
我们会在地球上再见的, 但愿会
We'll see you on Earth, I hope.
不, 不, 我们一定会的!
No, no, no. We will!
你可不可以…
Um, if you could just...
当然
Oh, yeah.
-根本没有希望
-This is hopeless.
我们不可能让那艘登陆舰飞起来的 留给我们的时间不多了!
We'll never get that dropship to fly, and we're losing time!
谁会知道他们会对史蒂文做些什么
Who knows what they're doing to Steven.
嗨, 史蒂文 我们该怎么--
Hi, Steven. - What are we going to d--
我回来啦!
I'm back!